[
    {
        "url": "https://www.nucnet.org/news/mou-could-lead-to-transportable-microreactors-for-mines-and-remote-communities-3-2-2024",
        "triplets": [
            {
                "head": "Des Nëdhé",
                "relation": "nationality",
                "tail": "Canada",
                "confidence": 1.0
            },
            {
                "head": "Des Nëdhé also said they planned to engage with Indigenous Peoples",
                "relation": "nationality",
                "tail": "Canada",
                "confidence": 1.0
            }
        ],
        "entities": [
            {
                "word": "Canada",
                "entity": "MISC"
            },
            {
                "word": "Prodigy Clean Energy",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "Des Nëdhé Group",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "Canada",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "Prodi",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "nuclear power plant",
                "entity": "REACTOR"
            },
            {
                "word": "Prodigy",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "T",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "Westinghouse",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "eVinci",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "Westinghouse",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "T",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "Prodigy",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "Canada",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "Prodigy T",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "TNPP",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "TNPP",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "small modular reactor",
                "entity": "SMR"
            },
            {
                "word": "Canada",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "T",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "Indigenous Peoples",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "Prodigy",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "Westinghouse",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "TNPP",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "Westinghouse",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "Westinghouse",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "Westinghouse",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "TNPP",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "e",
                "entity": "MISC"
            },
            {
                "word": "TNPP",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "Pro",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "Des Nëdhé",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "Indigenous Peoples",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "Canada",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "TNPP",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "Indigenous",
                "entity": "MISC"
            },
            {
                "word": "TNPP",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "Prodigy",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "NuScale Power",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "small modular reactor",
                "entity": "SMR"
            },
            {
                "word": "Prodigy",
                "entity": "ORG"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "url": "https://www.nucnet.org/news/ahead-of-brussels-summit-experts-outline-key-challenges-for-small-modular-reactor-commercialisation-3-4-2024",
        "triplets": [
            {
                "head": "Europe",
                "relation": "contains",
                "tail": "Brussels",
                "confidence": 1.0
            },
            {
                "head": "Yves Desbazeilles",
                "relation": "residence",
                "tail": "Brussels",
                "confidence": 1.0
            },
            {
                "head": "Alexander De Croo",
                "relation": "nationality",
                "tail": "Belgium",
                "confidence": 1.0
            },
            {
                "head": "Tim Yeo",
                "relation": "company",
                "tail": "NucNet",
                "confidence": 1.0
            },
            {
                "head": "UK",
                "relation": "contains",
                "tail": "Yeo",
                "confidence": 1.0
            },
            {
                "head": "Europe",
                "relation": "contains",
                "tail": "UK",
                "confidence": 1.0
            },
            {
                "head": "Europe",
                "relation": "contains",
                "tail": "UK",
                "confidence": 1.0
            },
            {
                "head": "France",
                "relation": "contains",
                "tail": "EDF",
                "confidence": 0.9399999976158142
            },
            {
                "head": "Europe",
                "relation": "contains",
                "tail": "Russia",
                "confidence": 1.0
            },
            {
                "head": "EIB",
                "relation": "company",
                "tail": "European Investment Bank",
                "confidence": 1.0
            },
            {
                "head": "David Brown",
                "relation": "company",
                "tail": "Wood Mackenzie",
                "confidence": 1.0
            },
            {
                "head": "Canada",
                "relation": "contains",
                "tail": "Poland",
                "confidence": 1.0
            }
        ],
        "entities": [
            {
                "word": "SM",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "G",
                "entity": "MISC"
            },
            {
                "word": "Nuclear Energy Summit",
                "entity": "MISC"
            },
            {
                "word": "NES",
                "entity": "MISC"
            },
            {
                "word": "Brussels",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "small modular reactor",
                "entity": "SMR"
            },
            {
                "word": "NES",
                "entity": "MISC"
            },
            {
                "word": "Yves Desbaze",
                "entity": "PER"
            },
            {
                "word": "New Nuclear Watch Institute",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "NNWI",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "London",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "NES",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "Belgium",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "Alexander De Croo",
                "entity": "PER"
            },
            {
                "word": "International Atomic Energy Agency",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rafael Grossi",
                "entity": "PER"
            },
            {
                "word": "IAEA",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "NNWI",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "Tim Yeo",
                "entity": "PER"
            },
            {
                "word": "NucNet",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "NES",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "UK",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ye",
                "entity": "PER"
            },
            {
                "word": "UK",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "SMR",
                "entity": "MISC"
            },
            {
                "word": "UK",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "SMR",
                "entity": "MISC"
            },
            {
                "word": "SMR",
                "entity": "MISC"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "UK",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ye",
                "entity": "PER"
            },
            {
                "word": "Rolls-Royce",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "France",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "EDF",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "SM",
                "entity": "MISC"
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "entity": "MISC"
            },
            {
                "word": "Italy",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "France",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "European Industrial Alliance",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "SMR",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ye",
                "entity": "PER"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "Russia",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "China",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "North America",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ye",
                "entity": "PER"
            },
            {
                "word": "European SM",
                "entity": "MISC"
            },
            {
                "word": "EU",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "EIB",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "European Investment Bank",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "EIB",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "Ye",
                "entity": "PER"
            },
            {
                "word": "NES",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "UK",
                "entity": "MISC"
            },
            {
                "word": "Wood Mackenzie",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "SMR",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "SMR",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "G",
                "entity": "MISC"
            },
            {
                "word": "NuScale",
                "entity": "MISC"
            },
            {
                "word": "SM",
                "entity": "MISC"
            },
            {
                "word": "David Brown",
                "entity": "PER"
            },
            {
                "word": "Wood Mackenzie",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "Poland",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "Canada",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "UK",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "South Korea",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "UK",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "Japan",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "entity": "LOC"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "url": "https://www.nucnet.org/news/government-could-complete-nuclear-project-audit-in-coming-weeks-3-3-2024",
        "triplets": [
            {
                "head": "Donald Tusk",
                "relation": "nationality",
                "tail": "Poland",
                "confidence": 1.0
            },
            {
                "head": "Bechtel",
                "relation": "company",
                "tail": "Westinghouse Electric",
                "confidence": 0.9800000190734863
            },
            {
                "head": "Pomerania",
                "relation": "contains",
                "tail": "Choczewo",
                "confidence": 1.0
            },
            {
                "head": "Poland",
                "relation": "contains",
                "tail": "Bando",
                "confidence": 1.0
            },
            {
                "head": "Pomerania",
                "relation": "division",
                "tail": "Poland",
                "confidence": 1.0
            },
            {
                "head": "Poland",
                "relation": "contains",
                "tail": "Warsaw",
                "confidence": 1.0
            },
            {
                "head": "Poland",
                "relation": "capital",
                "tail": "Warsaw",
                "confidence": 1.0
            },
            {
                "head": "Poland",
                "relation": "contains",
                "tail": "Pomerania",
                "confidence": 1.0
            },
            {
                "head": "Poland",
                "relation": "contains division",
                "tail": "Pomerania",
                "confidence": 1.0
            },
            {
                "head": "Poland",
                "relation": "contains",
                "tail": "Warsaw",
                "confidence": 1.0
            },
            {
                "head": "Poland",
                "relation": "capital",
                "tail": "Warsaw",
                "confidence": 1.0
            },
            {
                "head": "Pomerania",
                "relation": "division",
                "tail": "Poland",
                "confidence": 1.0
            },
            {
                "head": "Poland",
                "relation": "contains",
                "tail": "Warsaw",
                "confidence": 1.0
            },
            {
                "head": "Poland",
                "relation": "capital",
                "tail": "Warsaw",
                "confidence": 1.0
            },
            {
                "head": "Poland",
                "relation": "contains",
                "tail": "Pomerania",
                "confidence": 1.0
            },
            {
                "head": "Poland",
                "relation": "contains division",
                "tail": "Pomerania",
                "confidence": 1.0
            }
        ],
        "entities": [
            {
                "word": "Westinghouse",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bechtel",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "Polish",
                "entity": "MISC"
            },
            {
                "word": "Maciej Bando",
                "entity": "PER"
            },
            {
                "word": "nuclear power plant",
                "entity": "REACTOR"
            },
            {
                "word": "Poland",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "Donald Tusk",
                "entity": "PER"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bando",
                "entity": "PER"
            },
            {
                "word": "BiznesAlert",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "entity": "MISC"
            },
            {
                "word": "Westinghouse Electric",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bechtel",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "South Korea",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "France",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bando",
                "entity": "PER"
            },
            {
                "word": "Americans",
                "entity": "MISC"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lubiatowo",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "Kopalino",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "Choczewo",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "Pomerania",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "nuclear power plant",
                "entity": "REACTOR"
            },
            {
                "word": "Poland",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bando",
                "entity": "PER"
            },
            {
                "word": "small modular reactor",
                "entity": "SMR"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bando",
                "entity": "PER"
            },
            {
                "word": "Bando",
                "entity": "PER"
            },
            {
                "word": "Poland",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "Poland",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "Warsaw",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "Westinghouse",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "AP",
                "entity": "MISC"
            },
            {
                "word": "Lubiatowo-Kopalino",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "Pomerania",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "Poland",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "Poland",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "South Korea",
                "entity": "MISC"
            },
            {
                "word": "APR14",
                "entity": "MISC"
            },
            {
                "word": "Patnow",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "Warsaw",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "SMR",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "Orlen Sythnos Green Energy",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "Synthos Green Energy",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "PKN Orlen",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "SM",
                "entity": "MISC"
            },
            {
                "word": "Poland",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "KGHM Polska Miedz",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "small modular reactor",
                "entity": "SMR"
            },
            {
                "word": "Warsaw",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "Westinghouse",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "AP",
                "entity": "MISC"
            },
            {
                "word": "Pomerania",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "Poland",
                "entity": "LOC"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "url": "https://www.nucnet.org/news/westinghouse-poised-for-deployment-of-ap300-small-modular-reactor-3-2-2024",
        "triplets": [
            {
                "head": "Europe",
                "relation": "contains",
                "tail": "London",
                "confidence": 1.0
            },
            {
                "head": "Roman Romanowski",
                "relation": "company",
                "tail": "Westinghouse",
                "confidence": 1.0
            },
            {
                "head": "Westinghouse",
                "relation": "contains",
                "tail": "Romanowski",
                "confidence": 1.0
            },
            {
                "head": "UK",
                "relation": "contains",
                "tail": "Office for Nuclear Regulation",
                "confidence": 1.0
            },
            {
                "head": "UK",
                "relation": "contains",
                "tail": "Office for Nuclear Regulation and the Environment Agency",
                "confidence": 1.0
            },
            {
                "head": "UK",
                "relation": "contains",
                "tail": "Environment Agency",
                "confidence": 1.0
            },
            {
                "head": "England",
                "relation": "contains",
                "tail": "Teesside",
                "confidence": 1.0
            },
            {
                "head": "Georgia",
                "relation": "contains",
                "tail": "Vogtle",
                "confidence": 1.0
            }
        ],
        "entities": [
            {
                "word": "London",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "entity": "MISC"
            },
            {
                "word": "post",
                "entity": "MISC"
            },
            {
                "word": "Cop28",
                "entity": "MISC"
            },
            {
                "word": "small modular reactor",
                "entity": "SMR"
            },
            {
                "word": "SM",
                "entity": "MISC"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "London",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "SM",
                "entity": "MISC"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "UK New Nuclear Watch Institute",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "NNWI",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "NucNet",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "Europe",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "European",
                "entity": "MISC"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "Westinghouse",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "AP30",
                "entity": "MISC"
            },
            {
                "word": "Roman Romanowski",
                "entity": "PER"
            },
            {
                "word": "nuclear fuel",
                "entity": "FUEL"
            },
            {
                "word": "small modular reactor",
                "entity": "SMR"
            },
            {
                "word": "Romanowski",
                "entity": "PER"
            },
            {
                "word": "Westinghouse",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "AP1000",
                "entity": "MISC"
            },
            {
                "word": "AP300",
                "entity": "MISC"
            },
            {
                "word": "Romano",
                "entity": "PER"
            },
            {
                "word": "AP300",
                "entity": "MISC"
            },
            {
                "word": "AP1000",
                "entity": "MISC"
            },
            {
                "word": "AP300",
                "entity": "MISC"
            },
            {
                "word": "Westinghouse",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "AP300",
                "entity": "MISC"
            },
            {
                "word": "Westinghouse",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "AP300",
                "entity": "MISC"
            },
            {
                "word": "Westinghouse",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "NRC",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "US Nuclear Regulatory Commission",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "AP300",
                "entity": "MISC"
            },
            {
                "word": "AP300",
                "entity": "MISC"
            },
            {
                "word": "UK",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "Office for Nuclear Regulation",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "Environment Agency",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "AP30",
                "entity": "MISC"
            },
            {
                "word": "Teesside",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "England",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "Westinghouse",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "Community Nuclear Power",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "AP300 SMR",
                "entity": "MISC"
            },
            {
                "word": "AP100",
                "entity": "MISC"
            },
            {
                "word": "China",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "UK",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "US",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "Vogtle",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "Georgia",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "China",
                "entity": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "word": "Westinghouse",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "AP300",
                "entity": "MISC"
            },
            {
                "word": "AP1000",
                "entity": "MISC"
            },
            {
                "word": "AP1000",
                "entity": "MISC"
            },
            {
                "word": "I&C",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "safety",
                "entity": "POLITICAL"
            },
            {
                "word": "Westinghouse",
                "entity": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "word": "AP300",
                "entity": "MISC"
            }
        ]
    }
]